GAEL ZARCO

FULL-STACK WEB ENGINEER

A bi-lingual restaurant professional turned software engineer from Las Vegas. With 3+ years of education & experience in software, I have had the opportunity to work in start-ups, participate in hackathons, and develop a strong grasp of web development. I am seeking an entry-level position as a web engineer.

EDUCATION

University of Nevada Las Vegas, Las Vegas

Oct 2021 - July 2022

Software Development Bootcamp; 384 hours

College of Southern Nevada, Las Vegas

Aug 2019 - May 2021

Completed coursework towards AAS in Software Programming; 3.7 GPA

SKILLS

TypeScript React NodeJS REST APIs

HTML & CSS NextJS SQL & NoSQL Tailwind CSS

WORK EXPERIENCE

ANDROID APPLICATION DEVELOPER

Feb 2023 - Now

Decoding Greatness Inc, Remote (Part-Time | Contract)

- Undertaking the entirety of Android app development as a team of two utilizing Kotlin and Firebase.
- Self-teaching mobile development while building initial application infrastructure.
- Collaborate closely with team members and company owners to plan, design, and develop robust software solutions.

PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

TEAM LEAD | FULL-STACK ENGINEER

Feb 2023 - Mar 2023

LabLabAl, OpenAl Stack Hackathon ♦ Briefo

• My team-"Omni", received overwhelmingly positive feedback from project submission judges.

PROJECTS

Moxie ♦ Serverless, Full-Stack Social Media Application

Completed

NextJS, TypeScript, Tailwind CSS, tRPC, Clerk, MySQL, Prisma, PlanetScale, S3, Vercel

<u>Audix</u> ♦ Spotify Web Application

Completed

React, JavaScript, CSS, NodeJS, Express, Python, Flask, Spotify Web API

TOOLS

Mac & Windows VS Code Git Vercel

Postman AWS Canva & Notion Excalidraw

LANGUAGES

English - Native Spanish - Fluent

REFERENCES

Chris Bricker - Technology Architecture Senior Manager +1-303-919-7958 csbricker8@gmail.com

Accenture, Denver

Vinh Pham - Software Engineer +1-714-548-5677 merc_loiho@yahoo.com

Goodwill, Las Vegas

Christopher Bibbs - Web Developer +1-702-727-7828 cbibbs94@gmail.com

Aroma Retail, Las Vegas